

I am a professional software developer with over 15 years commercial experience in a number industries including banks, education, government and startups. Predominantly focused on Microsoft technologies such as .net / core, SQL but recently using more front end and open source technologies like Python, Scala, Haskell, Angular and Swift



0407928417



lucas@lucascullen.com



LinkedIn.com/in/lucascullen



111 Plumer St, Sherwood, QLD

EDUCATION

BACH OF MATHEMATICS QUEENSLAND UNIVERSTIY OF TECHNOLOGY 2010 — *

VARIOUS MICROSOFT CERTIFICATION (MCPD) 70-536:

70-536: 70-528:

70-547:

WORK EXPERIENCE

BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER ConsenSys / 2017 – 2018

ConsenSys is a remote first, distributed venture production studio using the Etheruem blockchain. I was hired as one of the first APAC employees to role out capabilities in the region.

- PegaSys spoke: Re write of the Etheruem client in Java. Also developed on JP Morgan's Quorom product in Go and Haskell
- Virtue Poker spoke: Distributed poker app using smart contracts, written in **Solidity**, **React-Redux** and **Electrum**
- Solutions spoke: Delivered a banking solution for Union Bank and other regional banks called project i2i using Solidity and TypeScript, hosted on Microsoft Azure and keys signing using their HSM. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LOP840hA9MY

CONSULTANT

Avanade - Accenture / 2015 — 2017

Created in April 2000 by two industry giants – Accenture and Microsoft – Avanade had one goal: deliver innovative services and solutions to enterprises worldwide using the Microsoft platform. My role as consultant was to help deliver on enterprise solution.

- Worked on project UBin in Singapore with the Singapore Monatory, authority and JP Morgan on their distributed ledger poc using Solidity and Microsoft Azure with Quorum. http://www.mas.gov.sg/Singapore-Financial-Centre/Project-Ubin.aspx
- Was invited to speak at "Tech Time" in Seattle, US on blockchain technologies on Microsoft Azure.
- Team lead for one of the delivery teams on the Australia Tax Office new tax portal. The build was a .Net / TypeScript / Knockout JS running on Microsoft Azure.

.NET SITE CORE ENGINEER – 6 MONTH CONTRACT RSL / 2015

The Returned and Services League, Australia (RSL) is a support organisation for men and women who have served or are serving in the Defence Force. I was brought on to help deliver upgrade their lotteries project.

 Interface a SiteCore CMS / ASP.Net MVC front end into their Microsoft Dynamics CRM

SHARE POINT DEVELOPER – 12 MONTH CONTRACT Zetta1 – Department of Education / 2014 – 2015

Zetta 1 where engaged to deliver a new "Learning Place" project built on top of the departments MS SharePoint role out

- Building MS SharePoint components.
- Using Azure notification services to push weather alerts.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER / TEAM LEAD Bank of Queensland / 2012 – 2014

- C# Microsoft SharePoint development.
- BizTalk integration with a SalesForce backend.

LANGUAGES / FRAMEWORKS / PRODUCTS

- | LANGUAGES
- .Net / .Net Core (c# F# vb.net)
- Solidty, Vyper
- TypeScript, Reac,t NodeJS
- Java
- Python
- Haskell, Scala, F#
- Ruby
- Swift, Objective C

- | FRAMEWORKS / PRODUCTS
- MS Azure, AWS, Digital Ocean, Heroku
- xUnit, nUnit
- SharePoint, SiteCore, Dynamics
- Azure Dev Ops, Team City, Jenkins
- Entity Framework, EF Core
- GitHub, BitBucket, TFS, Git, SVN